{
    "id": "83cf4ccfe84945d9885495d0bf91bf85",
    "title": "Relative Pronouns Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Jack, ................................. is my friend, is a good boy.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "whom",
                "that"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7159db1029be4127a470c4e3bf0f7436"
        },
        {
            "question": "Last year we visited Shimla ........................................ is perhaps the best hill station in India.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1d20b92766194a6fbaf294fbfcca1e88"
        },
        {
            "question": "This is the house .................................... I purchased from Peter.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "which",
                "whom"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c8c975ad980340178adae625f4d9d3cb"
        },
        {
            "question": "We bought some grapes from ................................... we extracted juice.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "whose",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9e55108657a0443196b0fa6f077a5394"
        },
        {
            "question": "He lent me a mattress on ................................. I slept soundly.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "which",
                "what"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "84279a12cf8e40c1a536e3eab88a389f"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have a friend .................................... mother works at a bank.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "whose",
                "who's"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4306fabfcdab40be97109858b9ebc63e"
        },
        {
            "question": "With ...................................... were you exchanging pleasantries?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "what",
                "whom"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "253f902422df47d8bc8c00da3e365ac2"
        },
        {
            "question": "We met a traveler .................................... bag was stolen.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "whom",
                "whose",
                "who's"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "153f9ebbaa9041439ff52af2c154cf74"
        },
        {
            "question": "Air, ..................................... is present everywhere, is essential for the existence of life.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "what",
                "whom",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "82ecb549bcec4d2585df13678987b0f5"
        },
        {
            "question": "Please try to understand ................................... I say.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "which",
                "that",
                "what"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "e771dc96a32f49418838e77e327affb5"
        }
    ]
}